<idea-plugin>
  <id>ru.fix.completable.reactor.plugin.idea</id>
  <name>Completable Reactor</name>
  <version>1.5-SNAPSHOT</version>
  <vendor email="kasfandiyarov@gmail.com" url="https://github.com/ru-fix">FIX</vendor>

  <description>
    <![CDATA[
      CompletableReactor framework makes it easier to create business flows that have concurrently running parts and complex execution branching.<br>
      CompletableReactor provides DSL-like Builder-style API to describe business flows.<br>
      Framework built on top of Fork Join Pool and CompletableFuture API.<br>
      <br>
      Completable Reactor plugin provide graph visualization and source code navigation within IDE.
    ]]>
  </description>

  <change-notes>
    <![CDATA[
      1.4.6 IDEA 2023.1 compatibility<br>
      1.4.5 Idea 2020.2 compatibility fix.<br>
      1.4.4 Add onElse transition<br>
      1.4.1 Support method templates<br>
      1.3.1 Remove support for old graph format<br>
      1.2.6 Support multiline title. Fix bug with displaying multiple endpoints for single vertex.<br>
      1.2.1 Add emptyMerger, routingMerger and mutator. Short coordinates declaration.<br>
      1.1.7 Fix Kotlin constructor parsing.<br>
      1.1.5 Support Kotlin graph.<br>
      1.1.3 Support sync handler.<br>
      1.1.0 New graph configuration format. Visualize graph directly from java source.<br>
      1.0.21 New graph items API: remove explicit id.<br>
      1.0.20 Fix graph zoom in IDE on MacOS. Remove Merge Groups.<br>
      1.0.18 Navigate to subgraph by clicking on subgraph node.<br>
      1.0.13 Fix update end point coordinates for detached merge points.<br>
      1.0.11 Remove MergeGroups from API. Implicit merge groups support.<br>
      1.0.10 Update completable reactor API. Fix coordinates update in java code.<br>
      1.0.6 Support merge point labels.<br>
      1.0.2 Support detached merge points.<br>
      1.0.1 Navigation to code from context menu and by double click.<br>
      1.0.0 Basic functionality of graph visualization and navigation.<br>
    ]]>
  </change-notes>

  <!-- Starting with 2020.2 JavaFX is deprecated in favor of JCEF. -->
  <!-- Dependency on "JavaFX Runtime for Plugins" is required to continue using JavaFX. -->
  <depends>com.intellij.javafx</depends>

  <idea-version since-build="202.6397"/>

  <actions>
    <action id="reactorGraphAction" class="ru.fix.completable.reactor.plugin.idea.ReactorGraphAction"
            text="Reactor Graph">
      <keyboard-shortcut first-keystroke="control alt R" keymap="$default"/>
      <add-to-group group-id="ToolsMenu" anchor="last"/>
    </action>
  </actions>

</idea-plugin>